atcomaart.com 2014-02-09

# Privacy Policy

|   
---  
|    
|  |  |  |  |  PRIVACY POLICY  
---|---  
|    
‘Atcomaart.com’ hereby referred to as the website follows a strict "Privacy Policy" as outlined below. At ‘Atcomaart.com’ we are committed to protect user’s personal and our business information. By accessing this website, you, as a website user consent to the collected works and treatment of information as submitted to us as follows. 

This "Privacy Policy" applies to all information that we collect through our website ‘Atcomaart.com’. We evaluate this "Privacy Policy" from time to time and if required, make the needed changes as per the needs and requirements and to become accustomed to varying industry and/or legal standards. We reserve the right at our sole discretion to make any modifications, alterations and/or update "Privacy Policy" at any time. Therefore, we thoughtfully request all, to check back periodically for the most up-to-date modifications.   
  
---  
  
  **Website Security  
**  
Atcomaart collects various types of information from all of its customers including visitors to Atcomaart.com Keeping security of sensitive information collected, is our prime concern. And, our website and software keep a secure eye on the activities of website traffic.

Please ensure to help us in maintaining the privacy. Please note that this "Privacy Policy" does not, in any way creates any contractual or legal right on behalf of any party and nor does it intends to do so in future.

The visitor information is collected through log files, including:

|  |  1\. IP Address.   
---|---  
|  2\. Browser type and language.   
|  3\. Access time.   
|  4\. Referring URL.   
|  5\. Navigation followed within website.   
|  6\. Duration of visit.   
|  7\. Links clicked.   
|  8\. Any other actions taken in connection with website and associated services.   
  
Collection of such information aids in calibrating website performance depending upon user behavior and consequently, structuring a safe and secure online business.   
    
  **Personal / Aggregate Information  
**  
Whenever any user provides ‘Atcomaar.com’ with assured contact information, together with name, contact number and a valid email address, it is kept confidential. However, but, this personal information is subject to use in order to send updates and/or vital news on the subject of changes to the website and/or company and to assess user/customer satisfaction with the worth of service provided, facilitate system administration and other informational uses.   
  
  **Use of the Information Collected**  
  
Atcomaart may choose to share information with third parties, such as suppliers, financial institutions, and third party service providers, and with any successor to Atcomaart's interest. ‘Atcomaart.com’ may also retain the content of the communications that are sent to Atcomaart customer service representatives. This information helps ‘Atcomaart.com’ to respond to inquiries regarding this Site.

‘Atcomaart.com’ also collects highly confidential personally identifiable and transactional information provided by companies and Site visitors that purchase products from the Site. This information includes shipping information, credit cardholder name and card number/expiration date.   

  **Information Disclosure**  
  
Atcomaart may disclose information about any Site visitor in response to subpoenas, investigative requests (with or without subpoena) and other legal process, to exercise Atcomaart's legal rights and defend against legal claims.   
  
  **Law Enforcement Agencies  
**  
 ‘Atcomaart.com’ has the right to disclose any personally identifiable information if:  |  |  • Required by law (via: warrant, or any sort of court order).   
---|---  
|  • To enforce our own privacy statement   
|  • To protect our customer’s rights   
|  • There is any case of any emergency that justifies disclosure of information   
  
Your information when shared with other bodies will be subject to their respective privacy policies.   
  
  Website Usage / Cookie Files   
  
We may accrue visitor data relating to referring domains, types of browsers used, operating system software, screen resolutions, color capabilities, plug-ins etc. This information may be stored in a cookie on your computer’s hard drive. Saving cookie in hard drive will not give us or any other website access to the rest of the computer. However, none of this information is personally identifiable and we will only share this information in the aggregate, reflecting over all website usage trends. Basically, cookies allow us to provide a more positive experience to users, including remembering their log in information to make access faster and easier on returning visits.   
  
**IMPORTANT NOTE:**  
  
If you configure your computer to block or erase cookies you will not be able to use this Site. Atcomaart also contracts with a third party data collection and reporting service ("Third Party Service") to collect information regarding Site visitors and their use of this Site. 

The Third Party Service uses Cookies to collect such information on behalf of ‘Atcomaart.com’. ‘Atcomaart.com’ uses this information to provide Site and service enhancements for customers and Site visitors. The Third Party Service is contractually prohibited from using information obtained in the course of providing these services to Atcomaart.com in any manner other than solely for Atcomaart's business purposes. Nevertheless, ‘Atcomaart.com’ respects your right to choose whether to be included in the services the Third Party Service provides to ‘Atcomaart.com’.   

  **General**  
  
We reserve the right to disclose any information in our sole discretion, reasonably necessary to conduct legal business and protect ‘Atcomaart.com’ and the business, without any prior permission, on warrant or other court order in certain situations, including but not limited to instances where users: |  |  1\. Have engaged in, or are alleged to have engaged in, any activity purporting to infringe upon the intellectual property rights of another;   
---|---  
|  2\. Are suspected of, or engaged in, fraudulent misrepresentation associated in any way with our website, business or site visitors.   
|  3\. Have engaged in, or alleged to have engaged in any other illegal or unsafe conduct or activity.   
  
  **Unsubscribe from E-Mail Marketing**  
  
Each Site visitor can unsubscribe from receiving e-mails containing promotional offers from ‘Atcomaart.com’ simply by sending a request indicating such desire to [contact@atcomaart.com](mailto:contact@atcomaart.com)  
  
  **Links**  
  
This website may be linked to other sites that are not owned, maintained or operated by Atcomaart.com and not subject to the same Privacy and other Policies. Atcomaart.com is not responsible for the content of those sites or the use of any information collected from you by those sites. The inclusion of any link to such sites does not imply any recommendation or sponsorship of such sites and Atcomaart.com disclaims any liability for links: (i) from another website to this Site, and (ii) to another website from this Site. 

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of information, we put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. We safeguard personal information, during electronic transfer from forms to our database, using encryption, security standards and procedures. We constantly review and if found beneficial, use new technology for protecting customer information on a regular basis. 

If you have any questions regarding privacy policy or your dealings with the website, or due to any reasons, you want to change or delete your personal information, provided already, please contact at [contact@atcomaart.com](mailto:contact@atcomaart.com)

**BY USING THIS WEBSITE, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF OUR PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE THIS WEBSITE.  
WE RESERVE THE RIGHT, AT OUR SOLE DISCRETION, TO CHANGE, MODIFY, ADD OR REMOVE PORTIONS FROM THIS PRIVACY POLICY AT ANY TIME. YOUR CONTINUED USE OF WEBSITE FOLLOWING THE POSTING OF CHANGES TO THESE TERMS MEANS YOU ACCEPT THESE CHANGES. **  

* * *
